http://www.asa100.com/legal%C2%A9/

ASA100
legal©
None of the photographic images on this site are royalty free or in the public domain. Please carefully read the Stulberg Photography Privacy Policy statement and Legal Disclaimers and Notices in their entirety before using this site. By using this site, you signify your agreement to the Privacy Policy statement, Legal Disclaimers and Notices, and the Terms of Use. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy Statement, Terms of Use, or Legal Disclaimers and Notices, please do not use this site. Website User Agreement These terms of use constitute a legal agreement between you and Scott Stulberg Photography ("Stulberg "). If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site. This site is owned and operated by Stulberg. All of the contents featured or displayed on this site, including, but not limited to photographs, images, downloadable graphics, moving images, text, illustrations and software ("Content"), are owned by Stulberg and/or its content providers. All elements of this site, including, but not limited to, the general design and the content, are protected by trade dress, copyright, moral rights, trademark and all other laws protecting intellectual property rights including contract law pursuant to this agreement. No content or portion thereof may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, scanned, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, without Stulberg 's prior written permission, except that you may view the content on any single computer monitor for review purposes only, provided you keep intact, without change all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices. Modification of the content or use of the content for any other purpose is a violation of Stulberg 's copyright, trademark, and/or other proprietary rights. The photographic images on this site are not royalty-free. You agree to indemnify Stulberg and its affiliates against all losses, liabilities, expenses, costs or damages, including reasonable attorneys' fees incurred by any or all of them as a result of your breach of the terms of this agreement or your unauthorized use of the content. Privacy Policy Statement Scott Stulberg and Scott Stulberg Photography and its web server, host, assigns and designees ("Stulberg ") utilize some or all of the following practices in regard to any information that Stulberg is provided or obtains about users of this website. You acknowledge that any information, personal or otherwise, transmitted to Stulberg by you may be used by Stulberg for any purpose, including dissemination or sale of such information to third parties. If you access another network or site through Stulberg, you may be subject to substantially different practices, including practices that govern your private email and dissemination of information that may affect your privacy. The transmission of information to or from this site may not be secure. Your further acknowledge that any information, personal or otherwise, transmitted to Stulberg by you by any means whatsoever may be used by Stulberg for the purpose of monitoring, policing and prosecuting claims for any suspected or actual violation of Stulberg’s copyright and/or other intellectual property or proprietary rights of any kind. Stulberg may share this information with legal counsel, investigators, other agents, or third parties. When you visit this site, Stulberg reserves the right to place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on your web browser and later retrieve. Stulberg reserves the right to use cookies to examine your web-surfing behavior before or after leaving this website. If you do not agree with the terms of Stulberg’s privacy policy statement, please do not use this site.  If you have any questions or comments concerning the above privacy policy statement, please contact Stulberg at scott@asa100.com. No modifications or changes to the privacy policy will be valid unless consented to in a writing signed by Stulberg. Legal Disclaimers and Notices Disclaimer This website and its content are provided "as is" and Scott Stulberg ") exclude to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law any warranty, express or implied, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of merchantability, satisfactory quality or fitness for a particular purpose. Stulberg does not warrant that the functions contained on or in this website will be uninterpreted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that this site or the server makes it available or free from viruses or other harmful components. Stulberg does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the content in this site in terms of its correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You (and not Stulberg) assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may or may not apply to you in whole or in part. Limitation of Liability Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to negligence, shall Stulberg be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the content in this site, or the site, even if Stulberg or Stulberg 's authorized representative have been advised of the possibility of such damages. Applicable law may or may not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability or incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you. In no event shall Stulberg’s total liability to you for all damages, losses, liabilities of any kind, and causes of action (whether in contract, tort (including, but not limited to, negligence) or otherwise) exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing this site. Other This agreement and all matters arising out of or relating to this agreement including but not limited to the use of this site and/or any content, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America, without giving effect to any principals of conflicts of law. You agree to personal jurisdiction by the Federal and State Courts located in Los Angeles County, California, United States of America. You further agree not to assert or interpose any counterclaims in any proceeding brought against you relating to this agreement. If any provision of this agreement and/or the terms of use of this site shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the subject matter herein and shall not be modified except in a writing, signed by Stulberg. Stulberg reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy Statement, Terms of Use, Legal Disclaimers, and Notices, and all other matters related to this site, including the information and any contractual license terms that may be featured on this site, without notice. Privacy Policy Statement, Legal Disclaimers, and Notices. © 2019 Scott Stulberg Photography All Rights Reserved.
replay introPHOTOGRAPHY WORKSHOPSONLINE WORKSHOPS previous workshop imagesAmazing BurmaBurmna workshop 2019Burma Workshop 2010Burma Workshop 2012Burma Workshop 2015Incredible IndiaIndia 2019 workshopIndia 2017 workshopOregon Coast workshop 2020The Palouse in WashingtonPalouse workshop 2019Palouse workshop 2017Palouse workshop 2016Palouse workshop 2015Palouse workshops 2014Palouse Workshop 2013Acadia National ParkAcadia National Park 2018Acadia National Park 2016Acadia National Park 2013 & 2014Italy 2017 workshopsDeath ValleyDeath Valley Workshop 2019Death Valley workshop 2017Death Valley workshop 2015Death Valley April 2014Death Valley October 2013Death Valley Workshop Oct. 2012Death Valley Workshop April 2012Death Valley Workshop 2011Death Valley Workshop 2010Milky Way panorama
2018Iceland 2018 workshopSouthwest 2017 workshopCamargue Horse workshopsCamargue Horse workshop 2014Camargue horse workshgop 2016Camargue horse workshop 2018Joshua Tree Workshop
2009Photographing the Figure
2010Sedona Creative Portrait
2018Nude in the Landscape Sedona 2015my book
Passage to Burmanew work & some favoritesfar away places
Paris
--
the city of lightsLa bella Italy Carnival in Venice, Italy Amazing BurmaEye candy of IndiaThe Greek Islands Prague
Czech RepublicIrelandDubaiIceland in WinterHong KongAfricaCambodiaThailand, Vietnam, Malaysia & JapanChinaTurkeyGalapagos IslandsCuba, Belize, Mexico & Costa Ricain the USASedona, ArizonaThe stunning landscapeAfter DarkOur beautiful home...The Amazing PalouseDeath Valley National ParkThe Stunning SouthwestThe Coast of OregonNew York CityLos AngelesCharleston, SCAcadia National Park in MaineSan Francisco & the coastVermont & Harvard 2011Lighthouses of Cape Cod Eye to Eyesome great faces...cool Leahcool Sydneybabies & belliesnight visionThe natural worldThe white horses of the Camargueover exposedmirror mirrorh2ostock photographypublished workimages on interior wallsImages for AndrewNew images for Andrew 3New images for Andrew 2New images for Andrew 1New for AndrewVenice for Andrewfall color for Andrew84 x 40 for AndrewNew York City 2017 for AndrewAndrew
18 x 53New Tests for UCLAgear List /
webinars /
software order printsmy blogclassesaboutcontactlegal©stock agencies
Site design © 2010-2020 Neon Sky Creative Media
